Allen D. Place, Jr. papers, Inclusive: 1989-1998, undated Bulk: 1991-1997
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Administrative Organizations, 1989-1998; 1
  - Task Force on Illegal Gambling, 1997; 4
    - Nevada, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - New Jersey, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - New Mexico, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - New York, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - North Carolina, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - North Dakota, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Ohio, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Oklahoma, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Oregon, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Pennsylvania, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Rhode Island, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - South Carolina, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - South Dakota, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Tennessee, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Texas Governor’s Task Force, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - United States, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Utah, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Vermont, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Virginia, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Washington, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - West Virginia, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Wisconsin, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Wyoming, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1991-1998; 2
  The Correspondence series ranges from 1991 to 1998 in chronology and is divided into two subseries, Individuals and Subject. Individuals includes correspondence with politicians, education representatives, and others concerned with political issues such as firearms and the treatment of inmates. This subseries is organized in alphabetical order.
  The Subject subseries consists of correspondence from the 72nd-75th Legislatures regarding topics such as education, school funding, redistricting, criminal justice reform, tort reform, and issues related to minors. Some inmate correspondence has been included in the subseries but is currently restricted. The materials in this subseries are organized in alphabetical order by year.
  - Individuals, 1991-1998; 1
    - Baskin, J. J., 1994 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Bentsen, Lloyd, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Gartman, Reba, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Gibson, Kenneth, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Hampton, Keith, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Mathis, James, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - McGaughy, Kyle, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Mize, Shane, Reverend, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Parker, Dick, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Perez, Noe E., 1998 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Roberts, Paul, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Ruiz, David, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Ruiz, David (1 of 3), 1995 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Ruiz, David (2 of 3), 1995 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Ruiz, David (3 of 3), 1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Saltsgives, Janet, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Tatum, Tommy, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Thompson, Richard, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Tillman, Katheryn, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Warren, Jimmy, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Subject, 1991-1998; 2
    - 72nd Legislature, Abortion, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - 72nd Legislature, Amnesty International, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - 72nd Legislature, Centralized Auto Inspection, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - 72nd Legislature, Clifton Elementary School, Thank You Letters, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - 72nd Legislature, Committees, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - 72nd Legislature, Conference on School Funding Legislation, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - 72nd Legislature, Copperas Cove, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - 72nd Legislature, Education, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - 72nd Legislature., Enterprise Zones, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - 72nd Legislature, Foster Care/Birth Control, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - 72nd Legislature, General, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - 72nd Legislature, General, 1991 January-February (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - 72nd Legislature, General, 1991 March-May (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - 72nd Legislature, General, 1991 June-December (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - 72nd Legislature, Greenhouse Effect, Toxic Air Emissions, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - 72nd Legislature, Health Human Services, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - 72nd Legislature, High Speed Rail Systems, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - 72nd Legislature, Hillsboro Day, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - 72nd Legislature, Letters from Allen D. Place, Jr., 1991 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - 72nd Legislature, Library Funding, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - 72nd Legislature, License Fees, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - 72nd Legislature, Licensed Vocational Nurses, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - 72nd Legislature, Prison Privatization, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - 72nd Legislature, Redistricting (1 of 3), 1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - 72nd Legislature, Redistricting (2 of 3), 1991 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - 72nd Legislature, Redistricting (3 of 3), 1991 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - 72nd Legislature, School Funding Out of District, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - 72nd Legislature, State Budget Plan, Sharp, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - 72nd Legislature, State Income Tax, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - 72nd Legislature, State Lottery, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - 72nd Legislature, State Schools Mental Retardation, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - 72nd Legislature, Teacher Retirement System, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - 72nd Legislature, General, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - 72nd Legislature, Mitchell, Joe K., Insurance Industry Houston Medical/Hospital Tort Reform, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - 72nd Legislature, Murder in Penal Institutions, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - 72nd Legislature, Prohibited Substances, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - 72nd Legislature, Public School Consolidation, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - 72nd Legislature, Regional Health and Human Services, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - 72nd Legislature, Regulation of Bail Bondsmen, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - 72nd Legislature, School Funding, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - 72nd Legislature, Worker’s Compensation, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - 73rd Legislature, Adolescent Pregnancy and Parenthood Advisory Council, Sex Education, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - 73rd Legislature, Comanche/De Leon Hospital Unification, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - 73rd Legislature, Communication Workers of America, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - 73rd Legislature, Dallas-Fort Worth Airport, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - 73rd Legislature, Electro-Shock Therapy, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - 73rd Legislature, General, 1993 January-March (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - 73rd Legislature, General, 1993 April-December (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - 73rd Legislature, Home-Rule School Districts, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - 73rd Legislature, House Memos, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - 73rd Legislature, Lobbyist Lists, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - 73rd Legislature, Penal Code Revision (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - 73rd Legislature, Penal Code Revision (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - 73rd Legislature, President Clinton’s Fiscal Year 1994 Budget, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - 73rd Legislature, Representative Allen Place Newsletter, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - 73rd Legislature, School Funding, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - 73rd Legislature, Coastal Management Plan, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - 73rd Legislature, Criminal Bill Update, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - 73rd Legislature, Death Penalty, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - 73rd Legislature, Drug Tax, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - 73rd Legislature, DWI Checkpoints, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - 73rd Legislature, Family Code Revision, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - 73rd Legislature, Federal Expenditures to Texas Fiscal Year 1993, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - 73rd Legislature, General, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - 73rd Legislature, Hamilton County Rural Public Transport, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - 73rd Legislature, Immigration, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - 73rd Legislature, Juvenile Justice, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - 73rd Legislature, Lawyer Advertising, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - 73rd Legislature, House Memos, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - 73rd Legislature, Penal Code Revision, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - 73rd Legislature, Texas Crime Justice Treatment Initiative, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - 73rd Legislature, Violent Crime Control & Law Enforcement Act, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - 73rd Legislature, Voluntary Castration, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - 74th Legislature, Automobile Theft Prevention Authority (ATPA), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - 74th Legislature, Airport Improvement Programs, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - 74th Legislature, Casino Gambling, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - 74th Legislature, Child Support Enforcement, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - 74th Legislature, Chiropractic, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - 74th Legislature, Commission on Children and Youth Legislation, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - 74th Legislature, Confined Animal Feeding Operation, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - 74th Legislature, Coryell County, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - 74th Legislature, Criminal Justice Reform, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - 74th Legislature, Department of Defense Closure and Realignment Recommendations, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - 74th Legislature, Department of Transportation Conditional Grant Program, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - 74th Legislature, District Satisfaction Questionnaire, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - 74th Legislature, Education, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - 74th Legislature, Elementary Grant Counselor’s Program, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - 74th Legislature, Family Planning Services, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - 74th Legislature, Frail Elderly Program, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - 74th Legislature, General, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - 74th Legislature, Illegal Aliens in Texas Department of Criminal Justice, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - 74th Legislature, Insurance Reform, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - 74th Legislature, Inter-governmental Correspondence, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - 74th Legislature, Judicial Reform, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - 74th Legislature, Justice for All Organization, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - 74th Legislature, Juvenile Crime, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - 74th Legislature, Juvenile DWI Laws, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - 74th Legislature, Lamar University Asset Transfer, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - 74th Legislature, Legislative Updates, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - 74th Legislature, Mothers Against Drunk Driving (MADD), 1995 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - 74th Legislature, Medicaid, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - 74th Legislature, Optional Retirement System, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - 74th Legislature, President Clinton’s Fiscal Year 1996 Budget, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - 74th Legislature, Property Rights/Home Equity, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - 74th Legislature, Public Utilities Regulatory Act, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - 74th Legislature, Redistricting, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - 74th Legislature, School Choice, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - 74th Legislature, School Funding, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - 74th Legislature, Student Loans, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - 74th Legislature, Substance Abuse Programs, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - 74th Legislature, Supreme Court — Opinion Public School Finance, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - 74th Legislature, Texas Business Advocate Survey Results, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - 74th Legislature, Teacher Pay Raise, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - 74th Legislature, Texas Natural Conservation Commission (TNRCC), 1995 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - 74th Legislature, Texas vs. Johnny Edward Hancock, Jr., Sexual Assault, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - 74th Legislature, Tort Reform (1 of 4), 1995 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - 74th Legislature, Tort Reform (2 of 4), 1995 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - 74th Legislature, Tort Reform (3 of 4), 1995 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - 74th Legislature, Tort Reform (4 of 4), 1995 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - 74th Legislature, University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - 74th Legislature, Vehicle Theft Act, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - 74th Legislature, Boykin, Gaston, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - 74th Legislature, Comanche County Library, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - 74th Legislature, Copperas Cove Independent School District, SB1 Videotaping, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - 74th Legislature, DWI, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - 74th Legislature, Ethics, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - 74th Legislature, Franchise Tax Avoidance, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - 74th Legislature, General, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - 74th Legislature, Juvenile Crime, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - 74th Legislature, Juvenile DWI Laws, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - 74th Legislature, Press Conference, Juvenile DWI and Sex Offenders, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - 74th Legislature, Shirley, Nelda June, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - 74th Legislature, Texas Issues, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - 74th Legislature, Texas Probation Association, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - 74th Legislature, U.S. Highway 84 Expansion Project, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - 74th Legislature, Warrantless Arrest, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - 74th Legislature, Weapons Laws, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - 75th Legislature, Age Limits on Hiring, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - 75th Legislature, Anti-counterfeiting Coalition, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - 75th Legislature, Bail Bonds, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - 75th Legislature, Brush Clearing, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - 75th Legislature, Code of Criminal Procedure, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - 75th Legislature, Comanche County, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - 75th Legislature, Comanche County Day, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - 75th Legislature, Concealed Carry, Ft. Hood, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - 75th Legislature, Copperas Cove Day, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - 75th Legislature, CPR Training, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - 75th Legislature, Electric Deregulation, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - 75th Legislature, Equine Infectious Anemia Test, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - 75th Legislature, Erath County Day, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - 75th Legislature, False Reports, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - 75th Legislature, Freund, Kay, Board of Pardons and Parole, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - 75th Legislature, General, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - 75th Legislature, Gun Bans, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - 75th Legislature, HB 1748 Non-Profits Receiving Sate Funds, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - 75th Legislature, Hill County Community Action Association, Incorporated, Head Start Programs, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - 75th Legislature, Hotel Tourism Taxes for Sports Stadium, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - 75th Legislature, Juvenile DUI/DWI Laws, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - 75th Legislature, Local Emergency Planning Committee, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - 75th Legislature, Mail Ballot, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - 75th Legislature, Mickey Mantle Foundation, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - 75th Legislature, Motorcycle Helmets, HB 366, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - 75th Legislature, Non-profit Board Elections, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - 75th Legislature, Nurses License Fees, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - 75th Legislature, Pretrial Release, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - 75th Legislature, School Finance Equity, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - 75th Legislature, Steve Davis Suspicious Death, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - 75th Legislature, Tarleton Intern, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - 75th Legislature, Tarleton State University, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - 75th Legislature, Tax on Horses, Mules, Work Animals HB 4, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - 75th Legislature, Teachers, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - 75th Legislature, Teacher Certification, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - 75th Legislature, Teacher Retirement System, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - 75th Legislature, Teacher Pay Raise, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - 75th Legislature, Telephone Deregulation, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - 75th Legislature, Telephone Surcharges, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - 75th Legislature, Texas Society of Professional Engineers (TSPE), 1997 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - 75th Legislature, Tort Reform, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - 75th Legislature, Val Verde County Voting Rights, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - 75th Legislature, Voting by Mail Procedures, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - 75th Legislature, Zero Tolerance Legislation, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - 75th Legislature, Consumer Complaint, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - 75th Legislature, Copperas Cove Fire Station General Obligation Bond, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - 75th Legislature, Dublin Bypass, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - 75th Legislature, Ephedrine, Texas Department of Health, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - 75th Legislature, General, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - 75th Legislature, Inmate Correspondence, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - 75th Legislature, State Bar/Death Row Representation, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - 75th Legislature, State Jail System, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - 75th Legislature, Stephenville Bridge Closure, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - 75th Legislature, Student Constituents Letters, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - 75th Legislature, Texas Department of Health, Texas Hazard Communication, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Legislative, 1991-1997, undated; 3
  The Legislative series, with materials ranging from 1991 to 1997, is divided into four subseries: the 72nd, 73rd, 74th, and 75th Legislatures. Each of these is further divided into at least two sub-subseries including General, Bills by Number, Correspondence, and Legislative Clipping Service.
  The General sub-subseries consist of daily reports, master lists, calendars, policies, and procedures, and are organized chronologically. The Bills by Number sub-subseries are arranged first by type of bill (i.e. House Bills, Senate Bills, and other bills) and then organized numerically by bill. Correspondence sub-subseries contain inquiries about the bills under consideration and are organized chronologically. The Legislative Clipping Service sub-subseries houses articles from various newspaper outlets used to research topics related to legislation. The final sub-subseries are arranged chronologically. Overall, the series is in good condition.
  - 72nd Legislature, 1991-1992; 1
    - General, 1991-1992; 1
      - Appointment Schedule (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Appointment Schedule (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Weekly Committee Schedule (1 of 3), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Weekly Committee Schedule (2 of 3), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Weekly Committee Schedule (3 of 3), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Master List of Bills by Author (1 of 3), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Master List of Bills by Author (2 of 3), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Master List of Bills by Author (3 of 3), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Master List of Bills by General Index (1 of 3), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Master List of Bills by General Index (2 of 3), 1991 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Master List of Bills by General Index (3 of 3), 1991 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Master List of Bills by Number (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Master List of Bills by Number (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - List of Bills Passed by Author (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - List of Bills Passed by Author (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - List of Bills Passed by General Index (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - List of Bills Passed by General Index (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - List of Bills Passed by Number, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Daily Floor Reports (1 of 2), 1991 January 8-March 27 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Daily Floor Reports (2 of 2), 1991 January 8-March 27 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Daily Floor Reports (1 of 2), 1991 April 2-25 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Daily Floor Reports (2 of 2), 1991 April 2-25 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Daily Floor Reports (1 of 2), 1991 April 29-May 10 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Daily Floor Reports (2 of 2), 1991 April 29-May 10 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Daily Floor Reports (1 of 2), 1991 May 13-17 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Daily Floor Reports (2 of 2), 1991 May 13-17 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Daily Floor Reports (1 of 2), 1991 May 20-27 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Daily Floor Reports (2 of 2), 1991 May 20-27 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Legislative Information System, Search Results Reports, 1991 June (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - First Called Session, Daily Floor Reports (1 of 2), 1991 July 15-August 13 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - First Called Session, Daily Floor Reports (2 of 2), 1991 July 15-August 13 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - First Called Session, List of Bills (1 of 2), 1991 July 15-August 13 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - First Called Session, List of Bills (2 of 2), 1991 July 15-August 13 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Second Called Session, Daily Floor Reports, 1991 August 19-25 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Second Called Session, Master List of Bills/List of Bills Passed, 1991 August 19-25 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Third Called Session, Daily Floor Reports, 1992 January (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Third Called Session, List of Bills/Bills Passed, 1992 January (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Third Called Session, House/Senate Daily Reports, 1992 January (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Fourth Called Session, Daily Floor Reports, 1992 November (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Fourth Called Session, List of Bills/Bills Passed, 1992 November (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Fourth Called Session, Daily House Calendar, 1992 November (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Bills By Number, 1991; 2
      - 72nd Legislature Amendments, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Legislature Committee Assignments, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - HR 317, Jonesboro High School Football Team, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - HR 318, Honoring Hillsboro Golden Eagle High School Band, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - HR 319, Congratulating Gatesville High School Band, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - HR 320, Congratulating Derrel Luce Baylor University Football Hall of Fame, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - HR 321, Congratulating the Valley Mills High School Football Team, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - HR 322, Congratulating the Clifton High School Football Team, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - HR 323, In Memory of Frank N. “Shorty” Smith, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - HR 419, In Memory of R. F. “Skinner” Wallace, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - HR 435, Recognizing April 11, 1991, Hillsboro Day in Texas (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - HCR 156, Silver-Haired Legislature’s Recommendation for Rural Crime Prevention for Elderly, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - HCR 186, Honoring Fort Hood and Personnel for Role in Operations Desert Shield and Desert Storm, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - HB 1, Appropriations for 1992-1993 Biennium, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - HB 9, Waiver of a Jury Trial Capital Offenses, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - HB 62, Motor Vehicle Insurance Reform, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - HB 1188, Aggravated Assault on a Governmental Employee, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - HB 1240, Sentencing Procedure in Capital Cases, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - HB 1775, Regarding Punishment and Procedures in Prosecution of a Capital Offense, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - HB 2813, Regarding County Court at Law of Cornell County, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - HB 2850, Civil Liability of Certain Chambers of Commerce and Volunteers and Employees of the Organization, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - SB 1, Summary, Recommended Appropriations for 1992-1993 Biennium, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - SB 9/HB 39, Capitol Police as Part of Department of Public Safety, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - SB 31, Redistricting, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 22)